simplifiedses.com 2010-11-29

# Privacy Policy

##### Privacy Policy

At Simplified Web Systems, we respect the privacy needs of our valued members. This Privacy Policy outlines what specific information is gathered on the Simplified Search Engine Suite and how that information is used.

Maintaining the privacy of your information is of paramount importance to us as it helps foster confidence, goodwill and stronger relationships with you, our members. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us.

###### Information Collection and Use

Simplified Web Systems, Inc explicitly asks when we need information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information"). Your personal information is used to create your personal access to our software, and to contact you in the course of using this software. Financial information that is collected is used to verify, identity and to bill either you or your company for products and services, as applicable. Demographic and profile data collected by Simplified Web Systems, Inc may be used to tailor this web site or any requested email communications, and to display information that is more relevant to you. Simplified Web Systems, Inc also compiles demographic and product use information, but in the aggregate only, and may make that aggregate information publicly available. Under no circumstances will Simplified Web Systems, Inc make any personal information about an individual user available to anyone.

Your email address is used to only send you information that you have requested. As part of your use of our software, Simplified Web Systems, Inc allows you to elect to receive, or not receive, certain information from Simplified Web Systems, Inc. Simplified Web Systems, Inc adheres strictly to permission-based email policy. Except as mentioned above, Simplified Web Systems, Inc will not send you unsolicited email information, commercial offers or advertisements. Simplified Web Systems, Inc will not sell, rent, or loan our contact lists or our member's contact lists (including member data) to any outside firms. All emails that you have requested will have an option to unsubscribe. Unsubscribe requests are fulfilled within minutes and no further communications will be sent to members who have stated that they do not wish to receive the specified information.

###### Communications from the Site

**Special Offers and Updates**

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify their new account and confirm their password. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Members can unsubscribe via the unsubscribe mechanism at the bottom of each email or through the "Email Preferences" panel in the Simplified Search Engine Suite Control Panel.

**Newsletter**

Out of respect for our member's privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications via the unsubscribe mechanism at the bottom of each email.

**Service Announcements**

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

**Customer Service**

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the member's wishes, regardless of their subscription status to receiving emails.

###### Policy Modifications

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when Simplified Web Systems, Inc makes changes to this privacy statement, we will highlight the changes on our homepage and email users who have given us permission to do so. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.

###### Contacting Us About Privacy

If you have any questions about our privacy statement, the information we have collected from you online, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact:

**Simplified Web Systems**  
Regarding: Simplified Search Engine Suite  
1670 Paonia St  
Colorado Springs, CO 80915
